Jorge Luis Azuara

Veracruz - Boca del Río, Ver. México | 232-114-62-20 | jorgeluisah47@gmail.com | github.com/robtzcraft

SUMMARY

Passionate Mechatronics Engineer and Software Developer with over 2+ years developing tools to automate tasks in different areas and process improvement. Experienced in working with different teams in different areas such as IT support and IoT teams, and sometimes working with robotics and electronics tools. Able to work independently of remote locations or in office environments as needed by the company.

EXPERIENCE

01/2022 to 08/2022

Teaching assistant

CETIS No.145 - Martínez de la Torre

- Assistance to students in understanding basic to advanced concepts of electricity, electronics, and robotics.
- Overseeing and mentoring students in their practical project work.
- Organization and maintenance of electricity laboratory equipment and materials.
- Collaborating with teachers to develop extracurricular lessons related to technology.

08/2023 to 07/2024

ServiceDesk and Automation Trainee

TENARIS-Tamsa – Veracruz

- Development of software tools for process automation.
- Analysis and improvement of technical procedures.
- PowerPlatform Development.
- Development of software tools for process automation.

08/2024 to 12/2024

HelpDesk Technical Specialist / Junior Software Developer

SharksIA - Veracruz

- Specialized technical support.
- PowerPlatform Development.
- Software/hardware troubleshooting and documentation.
- Software incident management.

12/2024 to Current

.NET / SQL Developer Jr.

SharksIA - Veracruz

- Software troubleshooting and documentation.
- Software Development and Implementation.

EDUCATION & COURSES

• UNIVERSIDAD VERACRUZANA

Mechatronics Engineer (Ago. 2018 - Jul. 2023) Specialization area: Embed systems and Artificial Intelligence.

FREECODECAMP

Machine Learning Roadmap (2022 - Present)

UDEMY

Non-Destructive Testing Level II - NTD Course (Udemy, 2022)

- HackTheBox Academy
 CREST CPSA/CTR Preparation (2023 Present)
- TENARIS UNIVERSITY

Citizen Developer (2024)

Skills

- Web Development (P/M) E-R-M stack (Intermediate)
- ASP.NET
- PlowerPlatform (PowerApps, PowerAutomate, PowerBl)
- SQL ⇒ PL-SQL / PostgreSQL / No-SQL MongoDB
- Python (TensorFlow / OpenCV)
- Autodesk Inventor / Fusion360
- Embed Systems (PIC & AVR based platforms)

Languages

- Spanish (NATIVE)
- English (B2 / C1*)
- Frech (A1)